[
  {
    "question": "1. Can a user save all database updates in onStop ()?",
    "answer1": "Yes, a user can save all database updates in onStop().",
    "answer2": "Due to low memory problem. your application will close before reaching onStop()",
    "answer3": "No, a user can save in a Bundle()",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "2.What are the layouts available in android?",
    "answer1": "Linear Layout",
    "answer2": "Frame Layout",
    "answer3": "Both are Correct",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "3. Which of these targets does Kotlin currently not support",
    "answer1": "LLVM",
    "answer2": ".NET CLR",
    "answer3": "JVM",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "4. How to store heavy structured data in android?",
    "answer1": "SQlite database",
    "answer2": "Shared Preferences",
    "answer3": "Cursor",
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "5. The ________ file specifies the layout of your screen. ",
    "answer1": "Layout file",
    "answer2": "Manifest file",
    "answer3": "Strings XML",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "6. How many ports are allocated for new emulator",
    "answer1": "2",
    "answer2": "0",
    "answer3": "10",
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "7. Does Kotlin have primitive data types, such as int, long, float?",
    "answer1": "No, Kotlin does not have nor use primitive data types",
    "answer2": "Yes, Kotlin is similar to Java in this respect",
    "answer3": "No, not at language level. But the Kotlin compiler makes use of JVM primitive for best performance",
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "8. What are the JSON elements in android?",
    "answer1": "integer, boolean",
    "answer2": "boolean",
    "answer3": "Number, string, boolean, null, array, and object",
    "correctAnswer": 2




  },
  {
    "question": "9. What does the .APK extension stand for",
    "answer1": "Application Package",
    "answer2": "Application Program Kit",
    "answer3": "Android Proprietary Kit",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "10.What operating system is used as the base of the Android stack? ",
    "answer1": "Linux",
    "answer2": "Windows",
    "answer3": "XML",
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "11. What does the !! operator do?",
    "answer1": "It converts any value to a non-null type and throws an exception if the value is in fact null",
    "answer2": "It's the modulo operator in Kotlin, similar to Java's %",
    "answer3": "it compares two values for identify rather than equality",
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "12.  When did Google purchase Android?",
    "answer1": "2007",
    "answer2": "2005",
    "answer3": "2008",
    "correctAnswer": 1

  },
  {
    "question": "13. Under which license is Kotlin available?",
    "answer1": "MIT",
    "answer2": "Apache 2",
    "answer3": "GPL",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "14. An open source standalone database",
    "answer1": "SQLite",
    "answer2": "BackupHelper",
    "answer3": "NetworkInfo",
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "15. Can a class be immutable in android?",
    "answer1": " No, it can't",
    "answer2": "Yes, Class can be immutable",
    "answer3": "Can't make the class as final class",
    "correctAnswer": 1
  }


]